[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "I mean, what are you picking up here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "are", "you", "picking", "up", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, look, there's certainly people who support Mubarak.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "there", "'s", "certainly", "people", "who", "support", "Mubarak", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "What was it like for to you go through that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "for", "to", "you", "go", "through", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, it's the first time that I felt threatened by sort of a mob, you know, walking my way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "first", "time", "that", "I", "felt", "threatened", "by", "sort", "of", "a", "mob", ",", "you", "know", ",", "walking", "my", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "What is wrong with doing that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, I don't know about right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Rudy, isn't the problem, though -- I mean do you agree that he is a dictator?", "question_tokens": ["Rudy", ",", "is", "n't", "the", "problem", ",", "though", "--", "I", "mean", "do", "you", "agree", "that", "he", "is", "a", "dictator", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Oh, I agree that he's a dictator.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "agree", "that", "he", "'s", "a", "dictator", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "You cannot have six months of these protests on the streets?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "not", "have", "six", "months", "of", "these", "protests", "on", "the", "streets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Hopefully we've done that.", "answer_tokens": ["Hopefully", "we", "'ve", "done", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "United States"]}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What would you do if you are now able to have any influence over this to protect Israel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "if", "you", "are", "now", "able", "to", "have", "any", "influence", "over", "this", "to", "protect", "Israel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think Israel has to do the same thing the United States does, which is it has to talk to Mubarak about as quickly as possibly -- as possible selecting somebody, a general or a group of generals, who can run an interim government, and also bring in, if they can, as they do that, people from civilian life, people from the protesters, but not the Brotherhood.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "Israel", "has", "to", "do", "the", "same", "thing", "the", "United", "States", "does", ",", "which", "is", "it", "has", "to", "talk", "to", "Mubarak", "about", "as", "quickly", "as", "possibly", "--", "as", "possible", "selecting", "somebody", ",", "a", "general", "or", "a", "group", "of", "generals", ",", "who", "can", "run", "an", "interim", "government", ",", "and", "also", "bring", "in", ",", "if", "they", "can", ",", "as", "they", "do", "that", ",", "people", "from", "civilian", "life", ",", "people", "from", "the", "protesters", ",", "but", "not", "the", "Brotherhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What are you thinking when you see that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "thinking", "when", "you", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "They're now war correspondents.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "now", "war", "correspondents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"]}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Why is this being done?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "this", "being", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Presumably it's because they're bringing the wrong message to the world which is that Mubarak's thugs, and I have to assume they're ordered by him or his people, they are trying to get rid of these protest, something, trying to stop this.", "answer_tokens": ["Presumably", "it", "'s", "because", "they", "'re", "bringing", "the", "wrong", "message", "to", "the", "world", "which", "is", "that", "Mubarak", "'s", "thugs", ",", "and", "I", "have", "to", "assume", "they", "'re", "ordered", "by", "him", "or", "his", "people", ",", "they", "are", "trying", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "these", "protest", ",", "something", ",", "trying", "to", "stop", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "What I don't understand is why President Obama isn't coming out now and stopping more bloodshed effectively by saying that's it, enough?", "question_tokens": ["What", "I", "do", "n't", "understand", "is", "why", "President", "Obama", "is", "n't", "coming", "out", "now", "and", "stopping", "more", "bloodshed", "effectively", "by", "saying", "that", "'s", "it", ",", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "POS", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, let me -- let try, you know, I'm hardly going to be the spokesperson for Mubarak.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "--", "let", "try", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "hardly", "going", "to", "be", "the", "spokesperson", "for", "Mubarak", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Wisner"]}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 249, "question": "What should you do, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "you", "do", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I think what he is doing is sending his emissary, Frank Wisner, who is a very --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "what", "he", "is", "doing", "is", "sending", "his", "emissary", ",", "Frank", "Wisner", ",", "who", "is", "a", "very", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "How many times can America go to war, say, with someone like Saddam Hussein and with Britain, by the way, calling him a dictator that treats his men badly while propping up people like Mubarak?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "can", "America", "go", "to", "war", ",", "say", ",", "with", "someone", "like", "Saddam", "Hussein", "and", "with", "Britain", ",", "by", "the", "way", ",", "calling", "him", "a", "dictator", "that", "treats", "his", "men", "badly", "while", "propping", "up", "people", "like", "Mubarak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "What some people have said is you have to think of what's in the best national interest of the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "some", "people", "have", "said", "is", "you", "have", "to", "think", "of", "what", "'s", "in", "the", "best", "national", "interest", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Saddam Hussein"], "LOCATION": ["America", "Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "I want to discuss now an extraordinary event in your life when very recently you discovered that you needed open heart surgery, which is a pretty dramatic thing to discover, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "discuss", "now", "an", "extraordinary", "event", "in", "your", "life", "when", "very", "recently", "you", "discovered", "that", "you", "needed", "open", "heart", "surgery", ",", "which", "is", "a", "pretty", "dramatic", "thing", "to", "discover", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Very dramatic.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "dramatic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Why more women than men?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "more", "women", "than", "men", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Whatever it is in their makeup -- women think that the biggest problem for them will be breast cancer.", "answer_tokens": ["Whatever", "it", "is", "in", "their", "makeup", "--", "women", "think", "that", "the", "biggest", "problem", "for", "them", "will", "be", "breast", "cancer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Did I say that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "I", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "You did.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Where did they get the new arteries from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "they", "get", "the", "new", "arteries", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Ace Hardware.", "answer_tokens": ["Ace", "Hardware", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "That moment when you knew that you had this big problem, and that you could potentially die if you didn't have the surgery, even for a tough cookie like you, what was going through your mind then?", "question_tokens": ["That", "moment", "when", "you", "knew", "that", "you", "had", "this", "big", "problem", ",", "and", "that", "you", "could", "potentially", "die", "if", "you", "did", "n't", "have", "the", "surgery", ",", "even", "for", "a", "tough", "cookie", "like", "you", ",", "what", "was", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "In my private life, I'm not such a tough cookie.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "my", "private", "life", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "such", "a", "tough", "cookie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Have you had an EKG?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "an", "EKG", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I'm going to talk to you about this when we come back.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "talk", "to", "you", "about", "this", "when", "we", "come", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Ivan, thank you for that report.", "answer_tokens": ["Ivan", ",", "thank", "you", "for", "that", "report", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "How interested should they be?", "question_tokens": ["How", "interested", "should", "they", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Well, the pictures are horrific, so you're interested just watching it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "pictures", "are", "horrific", ",", "so", "you", "'re", "interested", "just", "watching", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Could you imagine never going on television again?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "never", "going", "on", "television", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara"]}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Do you have a private life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "private", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, probably not as entertaining as yours has been, Barbara.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "probably", "not", "as", "entertaining", "as", "yours", "has", "been", ",", "Barbara", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "How long are you going to go on for?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "are", "you", "going", "to", "go", "on", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Well, I think I'll know when it's time to go.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "'ll", "know", "when", "it", "'s", "time", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What's been the single greatest interview?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "single", "greatest", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "You can't do that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "You are?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "What would he have made of what's going on in his country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "in", "his", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "He was also in a very difficult position.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "also", "in", "a", "very", "difficult", "position", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Who has been the love of your life?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "has", "been", "the", "love", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I have this little dog --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "this", "little", "dog", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "If I had five minutes to live, I would be with my daughter and closest friends.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "had", "five", "minutes", "to", "live", ",", "I", "would", "be", "with", "my", "daughter", "and", "closest", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Are you still on the dating scene?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "still", "on", "the", "dating", "scene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I've had a lot of special really very men in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "special", "really", "very", "men", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "But what would be the moment in your career, other than the Sadat, which is a great interview -- what would be the one moment in your career you would relive?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "would", "be", "the", "moment", "in", "your", "career", ",", "other", "than", "the", "Sadat", ",", "which", "is", "a", "great", "interview", "--", "what", "would", "be", "the", "one", "moment", "in", "your", "career", "you", "would", "relive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "I think the years in the Middle East.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "years", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sadat"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "But who's the person you never interviewed you wished you had?", "question_tokens": ["But", "who", "'s", "the", "person", "you", "never", "interviewed", "you", "wished", "you", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "There are people -- the Pope has never been interviewed.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "people", "--", "the", "Pope", "has", "never", "been", "interviewed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Wouldn't you like to do an interview with her?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "you", "like", "to", "do", "an", "interview", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I mean, 60 years of amazing secrets.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "60", "years", "of", "amazing", "secrets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Have you met Camilla?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "Camilla", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Yes, I have.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Are you excited about the royal wedding?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "excited", "about", "the", "royal", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Not enormously, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "enormously", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I'm taking my whole show there for a week.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "taking", "my", "whole", "show", "there", "for", "a", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "What is the last thing you think about when you go to bed?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "last", "thing", "you", "think", "about", "when", "you", "go", "to", "bed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "How early I have to get up in the morning.", "answer_tokens": ["How", "early", "I", "have", "to", "get", "up", "in", "the", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Do you have any regrets, real regrets?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "regrets", ",", "real", "regrets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "You know --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Do you think the death toll may rise?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "death", "toll", "may", "rise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Well, we've certainly seen an escalation in the use of force here during the first more than 12 hours of this battle here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'ve", "certainly", "seen", "an", "escalation", "in", "the", "use", "of", "force", "here", "during", "the", "first", "more", "than", "12", "hours", "of", "this", "battle", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]